{
    "id": "c8a9bf05408d44faa198207cae5d8f2d",
    "title": "Identifying Conditionals",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "If I don't drink tea in the morning, I feel sick.",
            "description": "In the zero conditional, we use a simple present tense in both clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "Zero conditional",
                "First conditional",
                "Second conditional",
                "Third conditional"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8cdf5deb18b949809cb277e33972628c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will talk to her if I meet her.",
            "description": "In the first conditional, we use a simple present tense in the if-clause and will + infinitive in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "Zero conditional",
                "First conditional",
                "Second conditional",
                "Third conditional"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1eb5618fc1504d2e824d1616788eaeac"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would have helped him if I had been there.",
            "description": "In the third conditional, we use a past perfect tense in the if-clause and would have + past participle in the main clause.\r\n\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "Zero conditional",
                "First conditional",
                "Second conditional",
                "Third conditional"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "2d2a994c7ccd45e1b3aab0bedc68738c"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I were you I would get that car serviced.",
            "description": "In the second conditional, we use a simple past tense in the if-clause and would + infinitive in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "Zero conditional",
                "First conditional",
                "Second conditional",
                "Third conditional"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4f06a496cebc4d1ca5b83824d892375a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wouldn't be surprised if she got married soon.",
            "description": "In the second conditional, we use a simple past tense in the if-clause and would + infinitive in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "Zero conditional",
                "First conditional",
                "Second conditional",
                "Third conditional"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d005dd7bd046403c854b78310e654ef9"
        },
        {
            "question": "If he arrives soon, we will go the movies.",
            "description": "In the first conditional, we use a simple present tense in the if-clause and will + infinitive in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "Zero conditional",
                "First conditional",
                "Second conditional",
                "Third conditional"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "eecb8da26b4c437aae05834e91ec0c35"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I had the time, I would bake a cake.",
            "description": "In the second conditional, we use a simple past tense in the if-clause and would + infinitive in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "Zero conditional",
                "First conditional",
                "Second conditional",
                "Third conditional"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d4be5cc1a071453582f8a2bbd218ffe5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would have handled the situation differently, if I had been in your place.",
            "description": "In the third conditional, we use a past perfect tense in the if-clause and would have + past participle in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "Zero conditional",
                "First conditional",
                "Second conditional",
                "Third conditional"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "83d5067a31664530a6f9f5ae175e2a94"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you had tried harder, you would have succeeded.",
            "description": "In the third conditional, we use a past perfect tense in the if-clause and would have + past participle in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "Zero conditional",
                "First conditional",
                "Second conditional",
                "Third conditional"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "7896e3b88c244a02940ef9cd6a377afc"
        },
        {
            "question": "If the team fails, the coach will be held accountable.",
            "description": "In the first conditional, we use a simple present tense in the if-clause and will + infinitive in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "Zero conditional",
                "First conditional",
                "Second conditional",
                "Third conditional"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0fcea07d04ef4a388745efc8a1279a54"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you had asked me, I would have told you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Zero conditional",
                "First conditional",
                "Second conditional",
                "Third conditional"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "98b5b4636075414aabbb5a3c3756cccb"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you had studied at a good college, you might have received a better job offer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Zero conditional",
                "First conditional",
                "Second conditional",
                "Third conditional"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a3e6556941814c1291bf3584896a4a17"
        }
    ]
}